workbloom.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

_At WorkBloom we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy describes the types of personal information that is collected and recorded by WorkBloom and how we use it.  Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here._

## Log Files

Like many other websites, WorkBloom makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

WorkBloom uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitors visit, and to customize our content based upon the visitors’ browser type or other information sent via their browser.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on WorkBloom.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to WorkBloom and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie at the following URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

## Our Advertising Partners

Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on WorkBloom and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

WorkBloom has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

## Third Party Privacy Policies

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. WorkBloom's privacy policy does not apply to and we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

## Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

## Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Thursday, August 28th, 2014.
